in this exercise we are told to
navigate to the directory above our my
folder directory
and delete all of the content we
generated with a single command
to navigate to the parent directory
we use the cd command and two dots
now we're in the parent directory which
is called exercises
and if i use ls to examine the contents
of this parent directory i see my folder
now one command used to delete a
directory
is rmdir
however when we try to use this we're
told that the directory is not
empty and therefore this command is not
going to
go through with deleting the directory
in order to delete a directory which is
not empty
in our case my folder has two ruby files
in it
we would use the rm command and
pass it a flag of capital r
this command can be very dangerous
because it's going to delete the
directory and
all of its contents if you do use this
command
be certain that you're in the correct
directory and that you don't need any of
the files contained within this
directory
so we'll execute this command and now
when we use
ls to examine the contents of the parent
directory
you can see that the my folder directory
is no longer there
it has been permanently deleted